Indiana University President's Office Correspondence, 1913-1937 C286
Indiana University Archives
- Subject files, 1913-1937 (Box 1)
  - Awnings, 1928-1933 (Box 19)
  - Ax, Alan D., 1929-1936 (Box 19)
  - Ax, John R., 1934-1937 (Box 19)
  - Axe, Harold (Box 19)
    - 1915-1923 (Box 19)
    - 1923-1937 (Box 19)
  - Axelrod, Sidney Rochland, 1930 (Box 19)
  - Axline, Elizabeth, 1925-1927 (Box 19)
  - Axt, Bertha, 1930-1937 (Box 19)
  - Axtell, Harry (Box 19)
    - 1913-1923 (Box 19)
    - 1923-1936 (Box 19)
  - Axtell, Ruth, 1926-1931 (Box 19)
  - Axtell, W.H., 1921 (Box 19)
  - Aydelotte, Frank (Box 19)
    - 1914-1918 (Box 19)
    - 1921-1936 (Box 19)
  - Aydelotte, Pres. Frank, 1926-1937 (Box 19)
  - Ayer, Callie, 1929-1931 (Box 19)
  - Ayer, Eloise Clement, 1919-1922 (Box 19)
  - Ayer, Evelyn V., 1925-1936 (Box 19)
  - Ayer, Helen C. (Box 19)
    - 1922 (Box 19)
    - 1924-1936 (Box 19)
  - Ayer, N.W. and Son (Box 19)
    - 1916 (Box 19)
    - 1931-1936 (Box 19)
  - Ayers, John H., 1929-1934 (Box 19)
  - Ayers, Lillie Marie, 1926-1928 (Box 19)
  - Ayers, Mina, 1933-1937 (Box 19)
  - Ayers, Thomas, 1934-1937 (Box 19)
  - Ayres, Bernice, 1930 (Box 19)
  - Ayres, B.W., 1920-1922 (Box 19)
  - Ayres, Elsie, 1932-1937 (Box 19)
  - Ayres, Frederick M., 1922 (Box 19)
  - Ayres, James G., 1921-1923 (Box 19)
  - Ayres, Judge A.C. (Box 19)
  - Ayres, K.D. 1916 (Box 19)
  - Ayres, Loren, 1926-1932 (Box 19)
  - Ayres, L.S. & Co. (Box 19)
    - 1913-1920 (Box 19)
    - 1921-1926 (Box 19)
    - 1927-1930 (Box 19)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 19)
  - Ayrshire Coal Co., 1925-1928 (Box 19)
  - Azar, Melvin, 1928-1935 (Box 19)
  - Azarraga, Francisco, 1916-1922 (Box 19)
  - Azen, Samuel Morton – SEE: R. H. VALENTINE, January 7, 1937 (Box 19)
  - Azimow, Rebecca, 1934 (Box 19)
  - Aznoe's Central Registry for Nurses, 1926-1936 (Box 19)
  - Baa- Bac, 1914-1937 (Box 19)
  - Baad, Dorothy B., 1932-1933 (Box 19)
  - Baade, Elmer, 1915-1916 (Box 19)
  - Baals, Mayor H.W., 1935 (Box 19)
  - Baas, Mrs. Elva Pittman, 1924 (Box 19)
  - Baatz, Wilmer, 1937 (Box 19)
  - Babb, Curtis T., 1933 (Box 19)
  - Babb, James E., 1916 (Box 19)
  - Babb, Jesse Leonard, 1930-1935 (Box 19)
  - Babb, Vernon W., 1931-1937 (Box 19)
  - Babbit, Arthur G., 1922 (Box 19)
  - Babcock, A.D., 1915 (Box 19)
  - Babcock, Beatrice, 1922-1928 (Box 19)
  - Babcock, Charles D., 1920-1931 (Box 19)
  - Babcock, Dean, 1914 (Box 19)
  - Babcock, Dena, 1915-1922 (Box 19)
  - Babcock, Kendric C., 1918-1920 (Box 19)
  - Babcock, Rushton & Co., 1916-1919 (Box 19)
  - Babcock, W.C. Grain Company, 1929-1932 (Box 19)
  - Babcock, W.C., Jr., 1930-1934 (Box 19)
  - Babcock & Wilcox Co. (see Babcock & Wilcox Tube Co.), 1914-1929 (Box 19)
  - Babcock & Wilcox Tube Co. (see Babcock & Wilcox Co.), 1930 (Box 19)
  - Baber, R.E., 1922-1927 (Box 19)
  - Babson Institute, 1919-1937 (Box 19)
  - Babylonian…, 1920-1927 (Box 19)
  - Baccalaureate, 1920-1937 (Box 19)
  - Baccus, Mary, 1921-1926 (Box 19)
  - Bach, Adeline P., 1925-1927 (Box 19)
  - Bach, Ephraim Lee, 1924 (Box 19)
  - Bach, Pedro, 1915 (Box 19)
  - Bachar, Gerald, 1933-1935 (Box 19)
  - Bache, J.S. & Co., 1919 (Box 19)
  - Bachelle, Cecil Fraser, 1931-1937 (Box 19)
  - Bacheller, Selma E., 1928 (Box 19)
  - Bachelor of Science…, 1932-1935 (Box 19)
  - Bachelor's Degree, 1928-1936 (Box 19)
  - Bachman, Charles C., 1914-1928 (Box 19)
  - Bachman, Frank P., 1921-1924 (Box 19)
  - Bachman, Harriet, 1933-1937 (Box 19)
  - Bachman, Irma, 1914-1923 (Box 19)
  - Bachman, K.R., 1929 (Box 19)
  - Bachtell, Vernon Orville, 1924-1936 (Box 19)
  - Bachtenkircher, Blanche, 1926-1931 (Box 19)
  - Bachtenkircher, Cecil, 1930-1931 (Box 19)
  - Back in the Jungle, 1929-1936 (Box 19)
  - Back, Lloyd Edison, 1919-1929 (Box 19)
  - Back, Robert Allen, 1935 (Box 19)
  - Back, Russel, 1920-1923 (Box 19)
  - Backer, Henry G., 1918-1921 (Box 19)
  - Backer, Herbert Joseph, 1934-1936 (Box 19)
  - Backert, Mary E., 1933-1934 (Box 19)
  - Backus, Florence Emily, 1923-1936 (Box 19)
  - Bacon and White, 1935 (Box 19)
  - Bacon, Charles M., 1927-1935 (Box 19)
  - Bacon, Mrs. O., 1917 (Box 19)
  - Bacon, Ruth, 1931-1937 (Box 19)
  - Bacteriology/Bacteriological, 1925-1937 (Box 19)
  - Bacus, Mildred Erina, 1919-1929 (Box 19)
  - Baa-Baz misc (Box 19)
  - Bad, 1914-1937 (Box 19)
  - Badders, Ara Carl, 1926-1929 (Box 19)
  - Badders, D.R., 1923-1924 (Box 19)
  - Badders, Mary, 1929-1932 (Box 19)
  - Bader, A.F., 1927 (Box 19)
  - Bader, Helen, 1928-1931 (Box 19)
  - Bader, Imogine, 1927-1928 (Box 19)
  - Badertacher, Darwin Ear, 1924-1931 (Box 19)
  - Badertscher, J.A., 1913-1923 (Box 19)
  - Badertscher, Jacob A., 1925-1937 (Box 19)
  - Badge, Charlotte Blodgett, 1926-1927 (Box 19)
  - Badger, Gladys S.C. (Sullivan Cunningham), 1918 (Box 19)
  - Badger, Henry Glenn, 1916-1937 (Box 19)
  - Badger, Richard G. (publisher), 1916-1932 (Box 19)
  - Badger, Ruth, 1937 (Box 19)
  - Badges, 1925-1927 (Box 19)
  - Badgley, Louise, 1931-1934 (Box 19)
  - Badollet, Marion S., 1919 (Box 19)
  - Badolette, Leroy, 1926 (Box 19)
  - Baenson, Emil, 1936-1937 (Box 19)
  - Baer, Alvin, 1937 (Box 20)
  - Baer, Charles, 1930-1932 (Box 20)
  - Baer, Charles Solomon, 1928-1936 (Box 20)
  - Baer, Dorothy, 1919-1921 (Box 20)
  - Baer, Floyd, 1918-1923 (Box 20)
  - Baer, Frederic L., 1928-1933 (Box 20)
  - Baer, Ivel, 1927-1934 (Box 20)
  - Baer, Joseph & Co., 1925-1934 (Box 20)
  - Baer, Louis, M.D., 1930-1936 (Box 20)
  - Baer, O.G., 1923-1927 (Box 20)
  - Baer, S.L., 1915 (Box 20)
  - Baer, Viola, 1932 (Box 20)
  - Baer, W.C., 1927-1929 (Box 20)
  - Bafford, William H., 1916-1937 (Box 20)
  - Bag/Baggage, 1917-1936 (Box 20)
  - Baganz, Crawford Norbert, 1924-1929 (Box 20)
  - Bagby, Lloyd C., 1930 (Box 20)
  - Baggerly, Clifford, 1928-1936 (Box 20)
  - Baggerly, Robin M., 1931-1935 (Box 20)
  - Bagnoli, Marie, 1924-1936 (Box 20)
  - Bagot, Free & Pence, lawyers, 1924-1925 (Box 20)
  - Bagot, Walter R., 1922-1923 (Box 20)
  - Bagshaw, Claude L., 1920-1934 (Box 20)
  - Bagshaw, James E., 1922-1928 (Box 20)
  - Bagwell, M.A., 1925-1929 (Box 20)
  - Bah-Baj (Box 20)
    - 1913-1919 (Box 20)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 20)
  - Bahne, Charles Frederick, 1925-1926 (Box 20)
  - Bahr, Max A., 1927-1932 (Box 20)
  - Bai (Box 20)
    - 1923-1928 (Box 20)
    - 1929-1932 (Box 20)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 20)
  - Bailek, Anthony J., 1930 (Box 20)
  - Bailey, Blanche, 1923 (Box 20)
  - Bailey, C.A. (Cleveland A.), 1924-1932 (Box 20)
  - Bailey, Chester Leonidas, 1913-1932 (Box 20)
  - Bailey, Mrs. Earl J., 1923-1925 (Box 20)
  - Bailey, Harold S. (Shock), 1929-1932 (Box 20)
  - Bailey, Helen, 1928 (Box 20)
  - Bailey, Henry S., 1924-1927 (Box 20)
  - Bailey & Himes Athletic Equipment, 1928-1932 (Box 20)
  - Bailey, Inez Holland, 1928-1932 (Box 20)
  - Bailey, Juanita, 1923-1924 (Box 20)
  - Bailey, Lawrence Stewart, 1925-1929 (Box 20)
  - Bailey, Lura Lee, 1932 (Box 20)
  - Bailey, Margaret N., 1924 (Box 20)
  - Bailey, Mary S., 1924-1927 (Box 20)
  - Bailey, Mazzie Vera, 1925-1932 (Box 20)
  - Bailey, Merlin M., 1926-1928 (Box 20)
  - Bailey-Mora Co., 1932 (Box 20)
  - Bailey, Paul, 1927-1929 (Box 20)
  - Bailey, Mrs. Ray, 1925-1927 (Box 20)
  - Bailey, Rush, 1928 (Box 20)
  - Bailey, Virgil I., 1929-1932 (Box 20)
  - Bailey, Virginia Carrington, 1929 (Box 20)
  - Bailey, Warren C., 1924-1927 (Box 20)
  - Bailey, Wilbur L., 1928-1929 (Box 20)
  - Bailhe, George, 1928 (Box 20)
  - Baily, Robert Kenneth, 1928-1931 (Box 20)
  - Bain, Auddra Marea, 1923-1924 (Box 20)
  - Bain, Edith, 1931-1932 (Box 20)
  - Bain, Robert Walker, 1924-1930 (Box 20)
  - Bain, Ruth, 1924-1932 (Box 20)
  - Baird, Dorothy Louise, 1931 (Box 20)
  - Baird, Edgar Lewis, 1929 (Box 20)
  - Baird, Gilbert, 1928-1932 (Box 20)
  - Baird, Lee O., 1926-1930 (Box 20)
  - Baird, Mary E., 1923-1931 (Box 20)
  - Baird, Melvin S., 1924-1930 (Box 20)
  - Baird, Ray A., 1926-1927 (Box 20)
  - Baird, Rodrester, 1924-1926 (Box 20)
  - Baird, Sarah Emily, 1930 (Box 20)
  - Bak (Box 20)
    - 1913-1917 (Box 20)
    - 1918-1920 (Box 20)
    - 1921-1923 (Box 20)
    - 1924-1926 (Box 20)
    - 1927-1929 (Box 20)
    - 1930-1932 (Box 20)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 20)
  - Baker, Carroll D.—Supervisor, Power Plant, 1934-1937 (Box 20)
  - Bala-Back 1913-1923 (Box 21)
  - Bal (Box 21)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 21)
    - 1927-1930 (Box 21)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 21)
  - Ball, W.C., 1918-1919 (Box 21)
  - Ball-Balz (Box 21)
    - 1913-1919 (Box 21)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 21)
  - Ball (Box 21)
    - 1923-1929 (Box 21)
    - 1930-1934 (Box 21)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 21)
  - Ball, George A. (Box 21)
    - 1919-1924 (Box 21)
    - 1925-1929 (Box 21)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 21)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 21)
    - Board Letters (Box 21)
      - 1935-1936 (Box 21)
      - 1936-1937 (Box 21)
    - Board of Trustees, 1936-1937 (Box 21)
    - Board of Trustees (Construction Matters), 1935-1936 (Box 21)
    - Board of Trustees Matters—Will of Hetsler, Ora, 1936-1937 (Box 21)
    - Correspondence (Faculty), 1936-1937 (Box 21)
    - Correspondence (Presidency of I.U.), 1936-1937 (Box 21)
    - Correspondence (Watkins Library: Wordsworth Collection), 1936-1937 (Box 21)
    - Fesler, James W., 1935-1936 (Box 21)
    - Gifts to I.U., 1936-1937 (Box 21)
    - Oakhorst, Muncie, Indiana (Box 21)
      - 1930-1931 (Box 21)
      - 1932-1933 (Box 21)
    - Olmsted Brothers, 1935-1936 (Box 21)
  - Ball Nurses' Home, 1927-1932 (Box 21)
  - Ball State Teachers' College, Muncie, Indiana (Box 21)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 21)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 21)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 21)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 21)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 22)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 22)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 22)
    - 1935-1936 (Box 22)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 22)
  - Bam-Bap (Box 22)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 22)
    - 1919-1923 (Box 22)
  - Ban (Box 22)
    - 1923-1930 (Box 22)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 22)
  - Banda, Hastings Kamuzu, 1928-1929 (Box 22)
  - Bara-Barn (Box 22)
    - 1913-1916 (Box 22)
    - 1917-1919 (Box 22)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 22)
  - Bar (Box 22)
    - 1923-1929 (Box 22)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 22)
  - Barbour, Humphrey M., 1918-1920 (Box 22)
  - Bark (Box 22)
    - 1923-1930 (Box 22)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 22)
  - Barker, Clare W.—Acting Dean, 1936-1937 (Box 23)
  - Barn (Box 23)
    - 1923-1928 (Box 23)
    - 1929-1932 (Box 23)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 23)
  - Barnhart, D.L., 1913-1914 (Box 23)
  - Barnhill, John F., undated (Box 23)
  - Bard-Barr (Box 23)
    - 1913-1919 (Box 23)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 23)
  - Barr (Box 23)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 23)
    - 1926-1931 (Box 23)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 23)
  - Barrett, Edward, 1913-1914 (Box 23)
  - Bars-Barz (Box 23)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 23)
    - 1919-1923 (Box 23)
  - Bart (Box 23)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 23)
    - 1928-1932 (Box 23)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 23)
  - Bas-Bat (Box 23)
    - 1913-1916 (Box 23)
    - 1917-1919 (Box 23)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 23)
  - Bas (Box 23)
    - 1923-1930 (Box 23)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 23)
  - Baseball Team Trip to Japan, 1922 (Box 23)
  - Basketball, Complimentary Tickets, 1935-1936 (Box 23)
  - Basketball Tournament, 1913-1916 (Box 23)
  - Bat (Box 23)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 23)
    - 1927-1930 (Box 23)
  - Bat (Box 24)
  - 1931-1937 (Box 24)
  - Batchelder and Scales, 1923-1924 (Box 24)
  - Bates, Frank G. (Political Science Department) (Box 24)
    - 1918-1921 (Box 24)
    - 1926-1932 (Box 24)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 24)
  - Batman, Gordon W., undated (Box 24)
  - Batman, Ira C. (420 E. 6th St. Bloomington, Indiana) (Box 24)
    - 1913-1919 (Box 24)
    - 1920-1925 (Box 24)
    - 1926-1930 (Box 24)
    - 1931-1934 (Box 24)
  - Bao-Baz (Box 24)
    - 1913-1919 (Box 24)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 24)
  - Bau (Box 24)
    - 1923-1929 (Box 24)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 24)
  - Bausch & Lomb Optical Company (Box 24)
    - 1913-1916 (Box 24)
    - 1917-1923 (Box 24)
  - Baxter, Neal Edward (Box 24)
  - Baxter's Studio (Box 24)
  - Bay (Box 24)
    - 1923-1930 (Box 24)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 24)
  - Bea-Beb (Box 24)
    - 1913-1919 (Box 24)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 24)
  - Be (Box 24)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 24)
    - 1925 (Box 25)
    - 1926 (Box 25)
    - 1927 (Box 25)
    - 1928 (Box 25)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 25)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 25)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 25)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 25)
  - Bec (Box 25)
    - 1913-1923 (Box 25)
    - 1924-1928 (Box 25)
    - 1929-1932 (Box 25)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 25)
  - Beck, Frank, 1936-1937 (Box 25)
  - Bed-Beg, 1913-1915 (Box 25)
  - Bed-Bek (Box 25)
    - 1915-1919 (Box 25)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 25)
  - Bed, 1923-1937 (Box 25)
  - Bedford Stone and Construction Co., 1913-1914 (Box 25)
  - Beede, J.W., 1913-1915 (Box 25)
  - Beh, 1923-1937 (Box 26)
  - Behrens, Gedward Behrens, n.d. (Box 26)
  - Bel-Bem (Box 26)
    - 1913-1918 (Box 26)
    - 1919-1923 (Box 26)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 26)
  - Beh-Bek, 1913-1915 (Box 26)
  - Bel (Box 26)
    - 1927-1931 (Box 26)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 26)
  - Ben, 1923-1930 (Box 26)
  - Benn (Box 26)
    - 1923-1930 (Box 26)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 26)
  - Bens, 1923-1937 (Box 26)
  - Benz, 1923-1924 (Box 26)
  - Benzel, Charles F., 1926-1928 (Box 26)
  - Ben-Beq, 1913-1918 (Box 26)
  - Ben, 1931-1937 (Box 26)
  - Ben-Beq, 1919-1923 (Box 26)
  - Benton, Guy P., 1913-1917 (Box 26)
  - Bergl, 1933-1934 (Box 26)
  - Bern, 1923-1937 (Box 26)
  - Berndt, A.H., 1913-1918 (Box 27)
  - Ber (Box 27)
    - 1913-1920 (Box 27)
    - 1920-1925 (Box 27)
    - 1926-1930 (Box 27)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 27)
  - Berr (Box 27)
    - 1923-1930 (Box 27)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 27)
  - Berry, Lillian G. (Box 27)
    - 1913-1914 (Box 27)
    - 1922-1923 (Box 27)
  - Bes-Bet (Box 27)
    - 1913-1919 (Box 27)
    - 1920-1924 (Box 27)
  - Bes, 1925-1937 (Box 27)
  - Betz, Frank S. Company, 1913-1914 (Box 27)
  - Beu-Bez, 1914-1923 (Box 27)
  - Beta Theta Pi, 1913-1914 (Box 27)
  - Beington-Williams, Inc. (1134-39 Indiana Pythian Building Indianapolis, IN), 1936-1937 (Box 27)
  - Bh, 1922-1923 (Box 27)
  - Bi (Box 27)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 27)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 27)
    - 1925-1926 (Box 27)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 27)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 27)
    - 1928-1929 (Box 27)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 27)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 27)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 27)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 27)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 27)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 27)
    - 1935-1936 (Box 27)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 28)
  - Bia-Big (Box 28)
    - 1913-1920 (Box 28)
    - 1921-1923 (Box 28)
  - Bible Chair (Box 28)
    - 1916-1917 (Box 28)
    - 1917-1918 (Box 28)
  - Biddle, James G., 1913-1914 (Box 28)
  - Biddle, Ward G. (Box 28)
    - Correspondence Regarding Football Tickets (Box 28)
      - 1933-1934 (Box 28)
    - Material sent to Dr. Bryan after Biddle's trip to Washington (Box 28)
      - 1934-1935 (Box 28)
    - Comptroller (Box 28)
      - 1935-1936 (Box 28)
      - September and October, 1936 (Box 28)
      - November, 1936 (Box 28)
      - December, 1936 (Box 28)
      - January, 1937 (Box 28)
      - February, 1937 (Box 28)
      - March, 1937 (Box 28)
      - April, 1937 (Box 28)
      - May, 1937 (Box 28)
      - June, 1937 (Box 28)
      - July, 1937 (Box 28)
      - August, 1937 (Box 28)
      - September, 1937 (Box 28)
    - Accounting systems recommended by the State Board of Accounts for the Bookstore, Residence halls, Commons and Practice House (Box 28)
      - 1937 (Box 28)
    - Publicity articles (Box 28)
      - 1937 (Box 28)
  - Bids, 1913-1917 (Box 28)
  - Biennial Report, 1920-1922 (Box 28)
  - Bierly, G. Remy, 1913-1920 (Box 28)
  - Big, 1923-1937 (Box 28)
  - Bigney, A.J., 1915-1917 (Box 28)
  - Bih-Bin, 1913-1923 (Box 28)
  - Bills, 1918-1920 (Box 28)
  - Bin, 1923-1937 (Box 28)
  - Bio-Biz (Box 28)
    - 1913-1919 (Box 28)
  - Bio-Biz (Box 29)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 29)
  - Bis, 1923-1937 (Box 29)
  - Bj, 1922-1923 (Box 29)
  - Bl (Box 29)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 29)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 29)
    - 1925-1926 (Box 29)
    - 1926-1927 (Box 29)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 29)
  - Bl (Box 29)
    - 1928-1929 (Box 29)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 29)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 29)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 29)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 29)
    - 1933-1934 (Box 29)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 29)
    - 1935-1936 (Box 29)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 29)
  - Bla (Box 29)
    - 1913-1915 (Box 29)
    - 1916-1919 (Box 29)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 29)
  - Black, W.W. (Box 29)
    - 1913-1915 (Box 29)
    - 1916-1920 (Box 29)
    - 1921-1926 (Box 29)
  - Blai, 1923-1937 (Box 29)
  - Blas, 1923-1936 (Box 30)
  - Ble, 1913-1923 (Box 30)
  - Bli, 1914-1923 (Box 30)
  - Blo (Box 30)
    - 1913-1920 (Box 30)
    - 1921-1925 (Box 30)
    - 1926-1928 (Box 30)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 30)
    - 1931-1933 (Box 30)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 30)
  - Bloomington Chamber of Commerce (Box 30)
    - 1915-1920 (Box 30)
    - 1921-1925 (Box 30)
    - 1925-1930 (Box 30)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 30)
  - Bloomington Country Club (Box 30)
    - 1916-1935 (Box 30)
  - Bloomington First (Box 30)
    - 1927 (Box 30)
  - Bloomington Kiwanis Club (Box 30)
    - 1931-1934 (Box 30)
    - 1934-1937 (Box 30)
  - Bloomington Rotary Club (Box 30)
    - 1927-1930 (Box 30)
    - 1930-1935 (Box 30)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 30)
  - Blu-Bly, 1913-1924 (Box 30)
  - Blu, 1925-1930 (Box 30)
  - Blu, 1931-1937 (Box 30)
  - Bo (Box 30)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 30)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 30)
  - Bo (Box 31)
    - 1926 (Box 31)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 31)
    - 1929 (Box 31)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 31)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 31)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 31)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 31)
  - Board of Trustees, 1918-1920 (Box 31)
    - 1921 (Box 31)
    - 1922 (Box 31)
    - 1923 (Box 31)
    - 1924 (Box 31)
    - 1924 (Box 31)
  - Boa-Bod (Box 31)
    - 1913-1914 (Box 31)
    - 1914-1915 (Box 31)
    - 1916-1923 (Box 31)
  - Board of Accounts, undated (Box 32)
  - Board Papers, Miscellaneous (Box 32)
    - 1923-1925 (Box 32)
    - 1926-1930 (Box 32)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 32)
  - Trustees of I.U. (Waiver of notice and consent to hold meetings), 1935-1936 (Box 32)
  - Bobbs-Merrill Company, 1913-1917 (Box 32)
  - Bock, D. Laurence, 1913-1915 (Box 32)
  - Bockstahler, Professor O.L., 1936-1937 (Box 32)
  - Boe-Bof, 1913-1919 (Box 32)
  - Boe, 1923-1937 (Box 32)
  - Bog-Bok (Box 32)
    - 1913-1917 (Box 32)
    - 1918-1923 (Box 32)
  - Boisen, Anton T., 1913-1935 (Box 32)
    Includes reprints "Schizophrenia and Religious Experience," from the Collected and Contributed Papers Published on the Sixtieth Anniversary of the Elgin State Hospital, December 1932; "Theological Education via the Clinic", Religious Education, March 1930; and "The Psychiatric Approach to the Study of Religion", Religious Education, March 1928. Search the IU Libraries catalog for electronic access to these reprints.
  - Boisen, Anton T., 1936-1937 (Box 32)
  - Bol (Box 32)
    - 1923-1928 (Box 32)
    - 1929-1937 (Box 32)
  - Bol-Bom, 1913-1923 (Box 32)
  - Bolser, C.M., 1924-1935 (Box 32)
  - Bon (Box 32)
    - 1913-1920 (Box 32)
    - 1921-1936 (Box 32)
    - 1926-1930 (Box 32)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 32)
  - Bonds (Box 32)
    - Sale of—material to sale of bonds for new buildings, 1935-1936 (Box 32)
    - For new buildings, building houses applying to buy bonds from (Box 32)
    - For new buildings on Indiana University Campus, 1936-1937 (Box 32)
  - Boo-Boq, 1913-1922 (Box 32)
  - Book, W.F. (Box 32)
    - 1913-1914 (Box 32)
    - 1914-1918 (Box 33)
    - 1919-1921 (Box 33)
    - 1922-1923 (Box 33)
    - 1924-1926 (Box 33)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 33)
    - 1929-1931 (Box 33)
    - 1932-1935 (Box 33)
  - Bookstore, I.U., Applications, 1923 (Box 33)
  - Bookstore, I.U. (Box 33)
    - 1914-1924 (Box 33)
    - 1925-1926 (Box 33)
    - 1927 (Box 33)
    - 1928 (Box 33)
    - 1930 (Box 33)
    - 1931 (Box 33)
    - 1932 (Box 34)
    - 1933 (Box 34)
    - 1934 (Box 34)
    - 1935-1936 (Box 34)
    - 1937 (Box 34)
  - Bookstore, I.U. - Annual Reports
    - 1923-1925 (Box 294)
    - 1925-1927 (Box 294)
    - 1927-1930 (Box 294)
    - 1930-1932 (Box 294)
    - 1932-1934 (Box 294)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 294)
  - Bookstore, I.U. - Manager's Book, 1924-1927
  - Bor (Box 34)
    - 1913-1920 (Box 34)
    - 1921-1925 (Box 34)
    - 1926-1928 (Box 34)
    - 1929-1932 (Box 34)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 34)
  - Bored Walk, 1932-1937 (Box 34)
  - Bos (Box 34)
    - 1913-1923 (Box 34)
    - 1924-1927 (Box 34)
    - 1928-1932 (Box 34)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 34)
  - Bot, 1913-1923 (Box 34)
  - Boo-Bov, 1913-1923 (Box 34)
  - Bou (Box 35)
    - 1923-1929 (Box 35)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 35)
  - Bow (Box 35)
    - 1913-1920 (Box 35)
    - 1921-1924 (Box 35)
    - 1925-1928 (Box 35)
    - 1929-1932 (Box 35)
    - 1933-1935 (Box 35)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 35)
  - Bowman, J.G., 1913-1915 (Box 35)
  - Boy-Boz, 1913-1923 (Box 35)
  - Boy (Box 35)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 35)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 35)
    - 1929-1932 (Box 35)
    - 1933-1937 (Box 35)
  - Boyd, David. R., undated (Box 35)
  - Br (Box 35)
    - 1923-1924 (Box 35)
  - Br (Box 35)
    - 1925-1926 (Box 35)
  - Br (Box 36)
    - 1927 (Box 36)
    - 1928 (Box 36)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 36)
    - 1931-1933 (Box 36)
    - 1934-1935 (Box 36)
    - 1936-1937 (Box 36)
  - Braa-Brac, 1913-1923 (Box 36)
  - Brackenmyre, J.H., 1920-1922; 1926 (Box 36)
  - Bradley, 1913-1923 (Box 36)
  - Brai, 1923-1937 (Box 36)
  - Brad-Bram, 1913-1923 (Box 36)
  - Bran-Braz (Box 36)
    - 1913-1920 (Box 36)
    - 1920-1923 (Box 36)
  - Branch, Eugene F., 1923-1925 (Box 36)
  - Bras, 1923-1937 (Box 36)
  - Brayton, A. W., 1928 (Box 36)
  - Brayton, James H., 1925-1930 (Box 36)
  - Bre (Box 36)
    - 1923-1928 (Box 36)
    - 1928-1932 (Box 36)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 36)
  - Brea-Brek, 1913-1922 (Box 36)
  - Brel-Brez, 1913-1922 (Box 36)
  - Bren, 1923-1937 (Box 37)
  - Brewer, Mary Morgan (Box 37)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 37)
    - 1930-1931 (Box 37)
  - Bret-Brez, 1923-1926 (Box 37)
  - Bri (Box 37)
    - 1923-1926 (Box 37)
    - 1926-1929 (Box 37)
    - 1929-1934 (Box 37)
    - 1934-1937 (Box 37)
  - Bria-Bril, 1913-1922 (Box 37)
  - Bridges on Campus, 1934-1937 (Box 37)
  - Brignall, C.S., 1936 (Box 37)
  - Brim-Briz, 1913-1922 (Box 37)
  - Brin, 1923-1934 (Box 37)
  - Bro (Box 37)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 37)
    - 1927-1931 (Box 37)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 37)
  - Broa-Brol, 1913-1922 (Box 38)
  - Broadcasting Material and Public Address System, 1924-1925 (Box 38)
  - Brom-Broz, 1913-1922 (Box 38)
  - Broo (Box 38)
    - 1923-1930 (Box 38)
    - 1931-1937 (Box 38)
  - Brooks, 1913-1922 (Box 38)
  - Brooks, Alfred Mansfield (Box 38)
    - 1913-1915 (Box 38)
    - 1916-1917 (Box 38)
    - 1918-1919 (Box 38)
    - 1920-1922 (Box 38)
  - Brooks, Elwood E., 1915 (Box 38)
  - Brophy, Byron J., Flandreau Indian School, 1932 (Box 38)
  - Brow (Box 38)
    - 1923-1925 (Box 38)
    - 1925-1927 (Box 38)
    - June, July, August, September 1927 (Box 38)
    - 1927-1929 (Box 38)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 38)
    - 1930-1932 (Box 38)
    - 1932-1935 (Box 38)
    - 1935-1937 (Box 39)
  - Brown, A, B, C, 1913-1932 (Box 39)
  - Brown, D-G, 1913-1922 (Box 39)
  - Brown, H-K, 1913 (Box 39)
  - Brown, L-O, 1913-1923 (Box 39)
  - Brown, P-S, 1913 (Box 39)
  - Brown, T-Z, 1913-1919 (Box 39)
  - Bru (Box 39)
    - 1913-1922 (Box 39)
    - 1923-1929 (Box 39)
    - 1930-1937 (Box 39)
  - Brumfiel, Daniel M., 1915-1916 (Box 39)
  - Brun, 1923-1937 (Box 39)
  - Bry (Box 39)
    - 1913-1922 (Box 39)
    - 1923-1927 (Box 39)
    - 1928-1931 (Box 39)
    - 1932-1937 (Box 39)
  - Bryan, Elmer Burritt, 1921-1934 (Box 40)
  - Bryan, Enoch A., 1928-1937 (Box 40)
  - Bryan, W.L. (Box 40)
    - 1913-1916 (Box 40)
    - 1917 (Box 40)
    - 1918 (Box 40)
    - 1919-1920 (Box 40)
    - 1921-1922 (Box 40)
    - 1923 (Box 40)
    - 1924 (Box 40)
    - 1925 (Box 40)
    - 1926 (Box 40)
    - 1927 (Box 40)
    - 1928 (Box 40)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 40)
    - 1931 (Box 40)
    - 1932 (Box 41)
    - 1933 (Box 41)
    - 1934 (Box 41)
    - 1935 (Box 41)
    - 1936 (Box 41)
    - 1937 (Box 41)
    - Acknowledgments of letter sent to 1923 graduates (Box 41)
    - Articles for Alumni Quarterly, student publications, speeches and notices and newspaper statements (Box 41)
      - 1923-1924 (Box 41)